blogonsisters.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Policy « Blog On Sisters – Start Your Global Conversation Today

Blogonsisters.com owns and operates the Blog on Sisters site. Blogonsisters.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. The purpose of this Blog on Sisters privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Blog on Sisters, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. This privacy policy applies to the Blog on Sisters site. Please note that this policy applies only to Blog on Sisters, and not to other companies’ or organizations’ Web sites to which we link. Our policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ changing needs. All changes to our privacy policy will be posted here so that you are aware of our current practices.

**Information**

Blogonsisters.com collects personal information when you register with Blog on Sisters and use our products or services. When you register we ask for information such as your name, contact information, email address, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Blog on Sisters and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Blogonsisters.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Blog on Sisters cookie information, and the page you request. All requested information on Blog on Sisters site is not required. You may choose to post additional information about yourself. Please do not post sensitive data such as credit card numbers, social security numbers or other personal data. Blogonsisters.com is not responsible for your disclosure of personal information on our forum, postings or other product offerings. You have the option to change your posted data at any time.

**Disclosure**

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Blog on Sisters or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. Blogonsisters.com may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. And we may share with our Web site partners and prospective customers aggregated statistical “ratings” information about the use of Blog on Sisters.

**Children**

Blogonsisters.com strongly supports the protection of the safety and privacy of young people. Blog on Sisters is a site meant for adult users and therefore we do not knowingly collect information about children.

**Protection of Data**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How to Contact Us**

We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, please contact [moderator@blogonsisters.com](mailto:moderator@blogonsisters.com)  
or writing to “blogonsisters.com, Attention: Blog on Sisters, 1001 G ST. NW, Suite 400E, Washington, DC 20001″.
